<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Business Analytics on Zihan Huang</title>
    <link>https://zihanhuang1.github.io/Zihan_Academic_Website/tags/business-analytics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Business Analytics on Zihan Huang</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 11:15:58 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://zihanhuang1.github.io/Zihan_Academic_Website/tags/business-analytics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Project XIV: Research Project - St. Christopher&#39;s Hospital for Children Process Mapping Project</title>
      <link>https://zihanhuang1.github.io/Zihan_Academic_Website/post/project-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 11:15:58 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zihanhuang1.github.io/Zihan_Academic_Website/post/project-14/</guid>
      <description>Date: April - June 2023&#xA;Right after I finished my master’s program, I worked as a research assistant with Dr. Hande Benson and Drexel Solutions Institute. We worked on a data analytics project aiming to help St. Christopher Hospital of Children in Philadelphia assess patient flow, examine opportunities for greater productivity and effectiveness to decrease LWOT (patients that leave without treatment), evaluate strategic opportunities and tools for staff communications about patients’ progress within the hospital system and streamline interrelated processes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Project XIII: Cooper Hospital Stroke Process Analysis</title>
      <link>https://zihanhuang1.github.io/Zihan_Academic_Website/post/project-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 11:15:58 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zihanhuang1.github.io/Zihan_Academic_Website/post/project-13/</guid>
      <description>Date: February - March 2023&#xA;This is a course project from my STAT-634 Quality &amp;amp; Six Sigma class, instructed by Dr. Edward Arnheiter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Project XI: Graduate Datathon 2023 - Supply Chain and Distribution Network Analysis with Under Armour</title>
      <link>https://zihanhuang1.github.io/Zihan_Academic_Website/post/project-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 11:15:58 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zihanhuang1.github.io/Zihan_Academic_Website/post/project-11/</guid>
      <description>Date: February 2023&#xA;Graduate &amp;lsquo;Datathon&amp;rsquo; is an annual, one-day event from LeBow College of business that partners with companies to solve their business questions through data analytics. The guest company for Datathon 2023 was Under Armour. Their business analytics group from Baltimore presented us with a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Project IX: Municipal Credit Disclosure via Natural Language Processing</title>
      <link>https://zihanhuang1.github.io/Zihan_Academic_Website/post/project-9/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2023 11:15:58 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zihanhuang1.github.io/Zihan_Academic_Website/post/project-9/</guid>
      <description>Date: September - December 2022&#xA;This is my capstone project, advised by Dr. Hande Benson. The capstone project is a 10-week business consulting project aiming to help MSBA students get exercise working on real-world business questions. This year we partnered with American Centuries Investments. Their business question for us was to develop a natural language processing model that can read municipal bond offering documents, extract core metrics, and build a rating model based on coefficients provided.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Project VI: Credit Risk Analysis on Mortgage Loan and Home Equity</title>
      <link>https://zihanhuang1.github.io/Zihan_Academic_Website/post/project-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 11:15:58 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zihanhuang1.github.io/Zihan_Academic_Website/post/project-6/</guid>
      <description>Date: June - August 2022&#xA;This is a business consulting project in the summer 2022, advised by Dr. Murugan Anandarajan and Chelsey Hill. In the project, we have a client from the real estate industry presenting us with two datasets, one for mortgage loan and one for home equity.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
