<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Zihan&#39;s Portfolio Website on Zihan Huang</title>
    <link>https://zihanhuang1.github.io/Zihan_Academic_Website/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Zihan&#39;s Portfolio Website on Zihan Huang</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 11:15:58 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://zihanhuang1.github.io/Zihan_Academic_Website/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Project XIV: Research Project - St. Christopher&#39;s Hospital for Children Process Mapping Project</title>
      <link>https://zihanhuang1.github.io/Zihan_Academic_Website/post/project-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 11:15:58 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zihanhuang1.github.io/Zihan_Academic_Website/post/project-14/</guid>
      <description>Date: April - June 2023&#xA;Right after I finished my master’s program, I worked as a research assistant with Dr. Hande Benson and Drexel Solutions Institute. We worked on a data analytics project aiming to help St. Christopher Hospital of Children in Philadelphia assess patient flow, examine opportunities for greater productivity and effectiveness to decrease LWOT (patients that leave without treatment), evaluate strategic opportunities and tools for staff communications about patients’ progress within the hospital system and streamline interrelated processes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Project XIII: Cooper Hospital Stroke Process Analysis</title>
      <link>https://zihanhuang1.github.io/Zihan_Academic_Website/post/project-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 11:15:58 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zihanhuang1.github.io/Zihan_Academic_Website/post/project-13/</guid>
      <description>Date: February - March 2023&#xA;This is a course project from my STAT-634 Quality &amp;amp; Six Sigma class, instructed by Dr. Edward Arnheiter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Project XII: Efficiency Analysis of English Premier League Players</title>
      <link>https://zihanhuang1.github.io/Zihan_Academic_Website/post/project-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 11:15:58 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zihanhuang1.github.io/Zihan_Academic_Website/post/project-12/</guid>
      <description>Date: February - March 2023&#xA;This is a course project from my OPR-620 Operations Research I class, instructed by Dr. Hande Benson.&#xA;As a sports fan and particularly a fan for English Premier League, I&amp;rsquo;m impressed by the data analytics team at Brighton &amp;amp; Hove Albion F.C. that evaluate player stats and make transfer strategies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Project XI: Graduate Datathon 2023 - Supply Chain and Distribution Network Analysis with Under Armour</title>
      <link>https://zihanhuang1.github.io/Zihan_Academic_Website/post/project-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 11:15:58 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zihanhuang1.github.io/Zihan_Academic_Website/post/project-11/</guid>
      <description>Date: February 2023&#xA;Graduate &amp;lsquo;Datathon&amp;rsquo; is an annual, one-day event from LeBow College of business that partners with companies to solve their business questions through data analytics. The guest company for Datathon 2023 was Under Armour. Their business analytics group from Baltimore presented us with a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Project X: Disney Released Movies Gross Income with Economic Factors Regression Analysis</title>
      <link>https://zihanhuang1.github.io/Zihan_Academic_Website/post/project-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 11:15:58 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zihanhuang1.github.io/Zihan_Academic_Website/post/project-10/</guid>
      <description>Date: October - December 2022&#xA;This is a class project from my STAT-628 Applied Regression Analysis class, instructed by Dr. Christopher Gaffney.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Project IX: Municipal Credit Disclosure via Natural Language Processing</title>
      <link>https://zihanhuang1.github.io/Zihan_Academic_Website/post/project-9/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2023 11:15:58 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zihanhuang1.github.io/Zihan_Academic_Website/post/project-9/</guid>
      <description>Date: September - December 2022&#xA;This is my capstone project, advised by Dr. Hande Benson. The capstone project is a 10-week business consulting project aiming to help MSBA students get exercise working on real-world business questions. This year we partnered with American Centuries Investments. Their business question for us was to develop a natural language processing model that can read municipal bond offering documents, extract core metrics, and build a rating model based on coefficients provided.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Project VIII: Research Project - The Effect of the Sunshine Act Reported Payments on the Utilization Rates of Interspinous Decompression Devices</title>
      <link>https://zihanhuang1.github.io/Zihan_Academic_Website/post/project-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 11:15:58 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zihanhuang1.github.io/Zihan_Academic_Website/post/project-8/</guid>
      <description>Date: June - September 2022&#xA;In summer 2022, I participated in a joint scholar program offered by Drexel University College of Medicine and LeBow College of Business that pairs MSBA students with M.D students for research programs. Advised by Dr. Michael Howley and Dr. Michael Weingarten, I worked with two M.D. students on their research programs. This is the second research project I worked with Anastasia Mityanina, a M.D student.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Project VII: Research Project - Continued Rise of Dizziness Presentation to U.S. Emergency Room</title>
      <link>https://zihanhuang1.github.io/Zihan_Academic_Website/post/project-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 11:15:58 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zihanhuang1.github.io/Zihan_Academic_Website/post/project-7/</guid>
      <description>Date: June - September 2022&#xA;In summer 2022, I participated in a joint scholar program offered by Drexel University College of Medicine and LeBow College of Business that pairs MSBA students with M.D students for research programs. Advised by Dr. Michael Howley and Dr. Michael Weingarten, I worked with two M.D. students on their research programs. This is the first research project I worked with Raz Garabet, a M.D student.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Project VI: Credit Risk Analysis on Mortgage Loan and Home Equity</title>
      <link>https://zihanhuang1.github.io/Zihan_Academic_Website/post/project-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 11:15:58 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zihanhuang1.github.io/Zihan_Academic_Website/post/project-6/</guid>
      <description>Date: June - August 2022&#xA;This is a business consulting project in the summer 2022, advised by Dr. Murugan Anandarajan and Chelsey Hill. In the project, we have a client from the real estate industry presenting us with two datasets, one for mortgage loan and one for home equity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Project V: A Data Mining Project on Telco Customer Churn Analysis</title>
      <link>https://zihanhuang1.github.io/Zihan_Academic_Website/post/project-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2023 11:15:58 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zihanhuang1.github.io/Zihan_Academic_Website/post/project-5/</guid>
      <description>Date: April - June 2022&#xA;This is a class project from my STAT-642 Data Mining class, instructed by Dr. Chelsey Hill.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Project IV: Customer Analytics on BookBinders Book Club Case Study</title>
      <link>https://zihanhuang1.github.io/Zihan_Academic_Website/post/project-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 11:15:58 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zihanhuang1.github.io/Zihan_Academic_Website/post/project-4/</guid>
      <description>Date: April 2022 - June 2022&#xA;This is a class project from my MKTG-606 Customer Analytics class, instructed by Dr. Michaela Draganska.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Project III: Graduate Datathon 2022 - Text Mining and Sentiment Analysis for Twitter Texts</title>
      <link>https://zihanhuang1.github.io/Zihan_Academic_Website/post/project-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 11:15:58 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zihanhuang1.github.io/Zihan_Academic_Website/post/project-3/</guid>
      <description>Date: February 2022&#xA;Graduate &amp;lsquo;Datathon&amp;rsquo; is an annual, one-day event from LeBow College of business that partners with companies to solve their business questions through data analytics. The guest company for Datathon 2022 was Harris Blitzer Sports &amp;amp; Entertainment, and their challenge for us was to analyze Twitter texts about New Jersey Devils from 2018 to 2020, give them a picture of what the fans are discussing on the social networks and their sentiment change through different time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Project II: Chronic Kidney Disease Case Study</title>
      <link>https://zihanhuang1.github.io/Zihan_Academic_Website/post/project-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 11:15:58 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zihanhuang1.github.io/Zihan_Academic_Website/post/project-2/</guid>
      <description>Date: January 2022 - March 2022&#xA;This is a course project on my STAT-630 Multivariate Analysis class, instructed by Dr. Matthew Schneider. The project was from the University of Virginia Darden College of Business. The project aims to perform multivariate analysis methods on the chronic kidney disease cases to understand the factors influencing whether a patient has such disease, and build predictive models to predictive CKD cases.&#xA;For the first part of the project, we used principal component analysis, factor analysis and cluster analysis to identify the key identifiers causing CKD.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Project I: Text Mining on Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows Part 2 Movie Script</title>
      <link>https://zihanhuang1.github.io/Zihan_Academic_Website/post/project-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 11:15:58 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zihanhuang1.github.io/Zihan_Academic_Website/post/project-1/</guid>
      <description>Project Date: September 2021 - December 2021&#xA;Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows Part 2 was the last episode of the legendary series. In this movie, Harry has finally grown into a steely lad on a mission to rid the world of evil, and the friends must search for the Horcruxes that keep the dastardly wizard immortal.&#xA;Our research objectives in the project included studying the overall sentimental change as the story develops, comparing the word and sentiment between the two centers of the story - Harry and Voldemort, comparing the sentiment between the movie and the book, analyzing through the movie reviews to find if the movie was too dark compared to previous series.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://zihanhuang1.github.io/Zihan_Academic_Website/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zihanhuang1.github.io/Zihan_Academic_Website/about/</guid>
      <description>My name is Zihan Huang, my journey of life started at a small town in northwestern China. After completing my undergraduate in Financial Engineering in Beijing, I made one of the most important decision in my life so far - transitioned into data analytics and came to the U.S. for graduate study during the covid times. As I finished my master&amp;rsquo;s program, I&amp;rsquo;m resolved to apply for a Ph.D. program in Decision Science/Operations Research/Business Analytics to devote myself to research work.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://zihanhuang1.github.io/Zihan_Academic_Website/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zihanhuang1.github.io/Zihan_Academic_Website/contact/</guid>
      <description>My contact information is as in these platforms:&#xA;Platform URL Email: zihhuangoff@gmail.com LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/zihan-huang-8018b622b/ </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
